<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Thoughts on Inner Daemons</title>
    <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/categories/personal-thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Thoughts on Inner Daemons</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 | For those Daemons inside us</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 03:46:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.innerdaemons.com/categories/personal-thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clueless</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/clueless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 03:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/clueless/</guid>
      <description>Here I am again. This time, with lots of “important” things sorted out: money, a loved one, health, a slightly more stable state of mind and yet, I still don´t know what is my true calling or where I should walk towards.
Lots of past decisions were built over an unstable foundation, based on fear and a sick need to be accepted or recognized. And, foolish me, I happily marched on putting together my life plan on top without even considering the assumptions I made were completely wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What´s the point?</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/whats-the-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 13:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/whats-the-point/</guid>
      <description>Thinking about the myriad of things I do in my life, this simple question popped out: What´s the point?
What´s the point of living? Of searching for the truth? Of trying to be happy? Of trying not to be sad? Of working? Of having hobbies? Of not having them? Of having sex? Of being celibate? Of traveling? Of being rich? Of being poor? Of being frustrated? Of being ecstatic? Of dying?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fears, daemons and survival</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fears-daemons-and-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 01:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fears-daemons-and-survival/</guid>
      <description>Yet again some disturbing news about planetary changes, chaos and catastrophe. I´m kind of fed up of this. Supposedly this is a good sign for a change of pace, direction and consciousness. But once more, nothing happens, just more of the same, life goes on with its injustice, crime, non-tolerance and fear, despite the general will to live better lives. Is it just me or we are headed for worse things day after day?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fearful Blues</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fearful-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 23:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fearful-blues/</guid>
      <description>It happens from time to time. Everything seems to be going smoothly and then, a dark and long shadow appears out of nowhere (well, it comes from the same place almost all the times), to haunt me yet again. I used to think that as long as I did well and the years just passed, accumulating experience, the shadow was less likely to return. I was wrong again. Perhaps the only thing left to do is to just accept its existence and deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye stranger</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/goodbye-stranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 23:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/goodbye-stranger/</guid>
      <description>I´ve just received what it seems to be her last message to me. It´s been a roller coaster, as usual. I cried a lot, I felt alone, I was in pain. The first and strongest impulse was to write and write and write some more. Her mail was short and somehow cold. It is perfectly understandable in our situation. She wanted to come back, to try things out again. She realized all the things we had together, in her own words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 01:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/freedom/</guid>
      <description>After a long time, finally I feel (somehow) free. No limits, no boundaries, just pure enjoyment and fun, sprinkled with small periods of apathy and tiredness. Nonetheless, the feeling of being able to do whatever I want with my time is an awesome experience.
It’s been a while since I spent one entire day sleeping, watching movies, nibbling food and just being present. Somehow I’m starting to understand my true nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A peaceful existence</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/a-peaceful-existence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 00:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/a-peaceful-existence/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago when I read his story about a marriage ending, I couldn’t help but wonder what was the sensation he was talking about like. It’s been almost three months since we decided to stop walking together and I must say I’ve regained a long lost feeling of peace, solitude, calmness and most important, my time is mine again.
Days come and go and I’m happy, healthy and learning gradually not to worry about small things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellusive Happiness</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/ellusive-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 04:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/ellusive-happiness/</guid>
      <description>Life is strange. The most important things happen in the wrong moments, it seems. One chapter ends, another begins but it feels like nothing it’s in place. There’s something always missing. Something not finished or not completely done. Why wait? I keep telling myself? Why not? Something inside me says “Let go, totally and freely. Don’t be afraid”, nonetheless when I feel so happy and comfortable with a supposedly “wrong situation” the question lingers again: “What should I do then?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fleeting moments</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fleeting-moments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 02:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fleeting-moments/</guid>
      <description>It’s kind of weird to feel I’m in the eye of the storm. She sleeps peacefully with our cat on her side and I feel free and content just for a brief period of time, feeling that all our problems, fights, disagreements, tears, sadness and crazy feelings just don’t exist. It’s like observing them from a far distance, watching them in a blurry fashion. Perhaps life is about these moments and nothing else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No worries</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/no-worries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 08:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/no-worries/</guid>
      <description>I just read this and thought it was worth to post it as a reminder of all of my false fears and stupidity. It´s a fleeting moment in the life of Steve Jobs, when he was still young with no money nor plans:
 We had very little money and no foreseeable prospects. One evening after we had splurged on dinner and a movie, we walked back to our car to discover a $25 parking ticket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The pursuit of happiness</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/the-pursuit-of-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 18:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/the-pursuit-of-happiness/</guid>
      <description>Just saw the movie and I must say I´m sad, angry, and most of all, disappointed. That story reminded me of my own current situation, and I didn´t like what I saw. What is the point of living in a deeply sick society, as Krishnamurti said, when nobody cares for you or your problems, where nothing you do seems to be useful or purposeful? What´s the point of having dreams, if all the system is designed to crush them all?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stillness</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/stillness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 11:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/stillness/</guid>
      <description>The moment of the week I like the most is sunday morning, when the sun has barely appeared on the horizon. I go out to our balcony and stare at the empty streets, wondering about why most days and life moments are not like this. No noise, no human beings on sight, no annoyances or distractions, only a deep and soothing silence mixed with the elegant movements of the trees in front of our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lacking air</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/lacking-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 20:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/lacking-air/</guid>
      <description>It´s been a long while since my last post. Paradoxically, I´ve been writing a lot for my job and other projects, but not here. Today is the day. Lately, a weird feeling is living with me almost permanently. The main effect is a generalized lack of air when I try to breathe. My chest aches and my head spins like crazy. When it happens, I try to study my surroundings, to determine what´s going on or what can be causing this, but the only conclusion that I´ve reached so far is that in the most cases, is triggered by anxiety or the though about having to do something I don´t really want to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Returning ghosts</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/returning-ghosts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 08:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/returning-ghosts/</guid>
      <description>It´s quite funny when those old viruses or daemons come lurking again to my mind. It can in the form of a mail message, a face, a voice or some special situation that points to me and triggers memories, sensations and more or less frequently, rage or sadness. I used to say that when you don´t see someone for quite a long time, you still think about this person as if time hasn´t passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Powerful Daemons</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/powerful-daemons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 10:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/powerful-daemons/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes is difficult to tame those daemons that have something to do with our more primal instincts: sex, rage or survival. These days I´ve been recalling a book I read many years ago, where the author described a society based on a closed-circuit life, this is, birth, life and dead inside a huge building, without ever going outdoors. People there were heavily divided by their abilities. The most successful ones lived higher, the others, lower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Worlds</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/two-worlds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 14:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/two-worlds/</guid>
      <description>It´s a strange feeling. In my last trips to my home land, when I return, I feel something like sadness, but it´s not quite that. Instead, is a mixture between past and future, friends and company, and loneliness and isolation. Perhaps it´s time to go back, perhaps not. It seems that time is passing quickly and I´m beginning to understand many things about my life. Now we have a dog. What is to come, is yet to be seen…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Not) All about my mother</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/not-all-about-my-mother/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 20:38:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/not-all-about-my-mother/</guid>
      <description>Don´t want to copy a bad movie title, specially being from him (her?). Lately, I´ve been realizing that some thoughts from long ago are true: my mom hates almost everyone. After my father´s death, she´s been immersed in a strange process of change, but not for good, I shall say, instead, her life is going into irrational hate and fear. I can´t even imagine what it is like to be in her position, her husband suddenly dead in a very painful way, but, instead of turning inside and closing the doors to the external world, the “lesson” should have been to be more kind, since life is too short to spend it fighting, feeling envy, hatred or remorse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Right now</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/right-now/</guid>
      <description>I haven´t written much in some time. A lot has happened. About a year has passed since I decided to take a sabbatical to gather myself again. In the meanwhile, I got married. She was the one, all the time, but I didn´t realize it until it was almost too late. I even crossed the ocean several times to beg for another chance.
I fought with my old daemons in a way I did not think I was able to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Envy</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/envy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 12:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/envy/</guid>
      <description>Today I saw his book in a store, and I felt miserable. Most of my life I´ve been ranting and complaining about almost all, but I haven´t accomplished none. To add insult to injury, I´ve realized that my “knowledge” about many topics is outdated or it doesn´t interest anyone now. I keep falling behind. But now I feel rage and sadness. No force of will to go on. In the other hand, I´m still waiting for that opportunity to come, patiently as instructed by many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The art of writing</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/the-art-of-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 20:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/the-art-of-writing/</guid>
      <description>Suddenly, I feel an urge to write down my thoughts, the things that happen in my life and the ideas that have been lurking into my mind for ages. It´s really nice to be into something, without pressure. To do it just for fun, as a way to put out many crazy ideas that cross my brain. Refreshing feeling. My plans are to continue, but who knows? The daemons can come back at any moment, sucking all my energy yet again…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Painful</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/so-painful/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2008 18:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/so-painful/</guid>
      <description>It´s really complicated to look into her eyes and not feel sadness. I know that we have to do it, but it´s so damn difficult. Being with her all these years has been a crazy ride: sometimes very good, others really bad. But at the end of the day, the bond between us is pretty strong, made with laughs, tears, sex and patience. Letting her go is the right thing to do, but I cannot help thinking in those good moments, the peace between us, her happiness and love for me, our travels (many of them without moving) and those “bed and book” afternoons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irrational Hate</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/irrational-hate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 18:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/irrational-hate/</guid>
      <description>I deeply hate her. But she doesn´t know. She´s there, happily living her life without knowing it. I haven´t told her about those things on my head, but I´m certain that she knows. I´m starting to think that I scare her, and that´s the reason for not acknowledging what´s going on. The worst thing is that she´s living with another person, and therefore, there´s no chance for anything. I don´t like not to have things under control, but this has a lot to do with my legendary shyness and stupidity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At last?</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/at-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2008 00:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/at-last/</guid>
      <description>Finally it happened. I´m leaving. It sounds kind of weird, since when I knew it, after the first feelings of relief, I got scared. Now what? I asked myself. But, strangely, I have started to stop thinking about what´s next. I only want to stop. To breathe. To stop worrying about everything. I won´t miss the things I´m going to left behind: no friends, no valuable relationships, no good moments. Nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life goes on</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/life-goes-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2007 18:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/life-goes-on/</guid>
      <description>Today I received some news about my ex-wife. She´s pregnant. It´s kind of strange, since I haven´t talked with her for many months, and the last time this occurred, she told me that she didn´t want to speak with me anymore. We used to be friends after breaking up, but then things went wrong. My feelings are a mixture at this time. I hope she´s ok, and her partner (if any) is a good person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Endless circle full of cockroaches</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/endless-circle-full-of-cockroaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2007 10:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/endless-circle-full-of-cockroaches/</guid>
      <description>This title can be a little weird, but it describes perfectly my current situation. I feel trapped, but not by the circumstances, but by myself. I feel that I lack the will or determination to break free. I have now more clear ideas about where I want to go, or what I want to do, but future is still looking blurry. I´ve been offered another project at my company, but the fact is that I don´t want to be here anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Hole</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/black-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 10:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/black-hole/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago, a close friend told me that whenever he arrived at the town where he lives, he felt that his energy levels drained fast. Something similar happens to me at my office. It´s like a black hole. No matter how energetic I wake up in the morning: in the moment that I sit down in my desk, all vanishes… Perhaps it´s time to seek new challenges somewhere else. It´s really bad not to have energy to pursue my own interests, and not only the company ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Almost) Hopeless</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/almost-hopeless/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2007 11:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/almost-hopeless/</guid>
      <description>Some days have passed since I received the news about my fathers´ death. Perhaps this is not the best moment to write, but somehow it soothes me and helps to relieve the pain. It´s kind of strange, but this has made me think about life and death, my role in this world, my attitudes towards the rest of the people surrounding me, my mistakes, my goals, my dreams, the futility of many stupid things that, we believe, are important, the fragility of life, the moments that are running fast past behind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The right to be wrong</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/right-or-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 19:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/right-or-wrong/</guid>
      <description>The main problem of having a lot of spare time is that you tend to think too much about the same things. Decisions that you´ve already made, choices or plans already underway. Everything goes under a cruel scrutiny, trying to find that glitch or error (inexistent, most of the time) that causes disconfort, fear or depression. It´s kind of hard to trust ourselves, to close our eyes and walk believing in our choices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Time</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/big-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2006 21:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/big-time/</guid>
      <description>Andy Warhol said that every one of us has the right to enjoy 15 minutes of fame. I think my time has come and I don´t want to pass. You only live once (not twice, like Mr. Bond used to say), and I stopped thinking about stupid things at last! I´m motivated, happy and confident…
Enjoy: A simple word but quite complicated to apply. Ready or not, here I come…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Again?</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2006 20:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/again/</guid>
      <description>Kind of weird to post this, but I´m considering to do it once more. Something says that this time is gonna be ok, but it still is a strange sensation. Perhaps I found the right partner. In 23 days I´ll find out. In the meantime, I´m really excited, and for the first time in ages, happy…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Off Daemons</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/time-off-daemons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 08:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/time-off-daemons/</guid>
      <description>This can sound quite funny, to say the least, but 4 weeks have passed since the accident, and I´m still struggling to start many “queued” things on my head. Now I´m not annoyed anymore: I´m officially worried. I´ve been listening to some specialized “entrainment” sessions to try and reduce my depression, and, despite some minor improvements, I feel more or less the same: without energy and motivation to move on. It´s kind of scary not to know where are you headed, and to continue doing the same things like a robot, because there is nothing better out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broken knee</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/broken-knee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2006 19:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/broken-knee/</guid>
      <description>Some days ago I fell from a Mountain Board and broke my left knee. It was painful, but now I finally have some time off (if I decide to shut down my Office VPN connection, of course).
By the way, today I decided to shave my head. It was something I wanted to do a long time ago, and the chance just appeared. No prying eyes, no roles to play, perfect!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Void</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/void/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2006 16:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/void/</guid>
      <description>Yet another week. More complaining, more tiredness, more and more of the same things. Sometimes, life is like an old movie, moving slowly and without sound to nowhere. I´ve recently discovered that many of my life certainties are not there anymore. I try to start over, to correct my past mistakes, but I simply can´t find the required energy to do so. Perhaps it´s time to seek some help. The bad part is that when I did this in the past, I ended feeling worse, and all my problems remained more or less the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alone</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2006 10:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/alone/</guid>
      <description>What does it feel like to know that almost everything you believe in, or the things you like, are a fake? Every day, I realize that the world that I used to believe I live in, it´s not there anymore. Friends are inexistent, people that you think is there, isn´t. The feeling of belonging to anything vanishes slowly, leaving a big void of loneliness and sadness. No lasting relationships with friends or loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s there</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/its-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2006 22:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/its-there/</guid>
      <description>The problem is that it´s not reachable by any means. You try to realize a strategy, but it’s useless. Usually, you’re late. Very late. Some thug has already picked up what you think is yours, and there’s nothing left to be done. Only shame and retreat. It’s becoming so familiar that´s kind of scary. I think I must change my way of judging the world in order to fit in. It’s difficult, but it has to be done, otherwise, I’ll be left behind, alone…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekends</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/weekends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 23:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/weekends/</guid>
      <description>I adore weekends, but not for the same reasons regular people say they’re good (partying, drinking and so on). I like them mostly for the possibility of having time only for me, without constraints nor rules. It’s almost 2 AM on saturday and I’m wide awake, thrashing around with my laptop, without worrying about getting up late the next day. I simply cannot cope with someone else telling me what to do, at what time should I arrive and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ads</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2006 23:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/ads/</guid>
      <description>I hate ads. Their simple vision about reaching happiness by using some sort of “snake oil” product or buying a brand new fuc.ing car, makes me sick. Everytime I think about all the people that even doesn’t have a TV set to watch them, I almost cry. How will an unemployed person feel about not having the money or the power or the looks to be accepted? I remember this Simpsons episode (Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inner Peace</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/inner-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 18:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/inner-peace/</guid>
      <description>It´s a bit funny, but the simplest thing that has happened in my life is the one that have been leading me through the road of insight and self-knowledge. Some people have helped, of course (thanks L, for those marvelous book suggestions), but the “core” of everything is simply wanting to know more and be more aware of the present. A fascinating trip so far…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scary Plans</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/scary-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2005 18:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/scary-plans/</guid>
      <description>This might sound a little funny, but, while other people enjoy inmensely doing future plans, this thing scares the hell out of me. Just to think in all the changes, worries, loneliless, possible lack of money, a hostile environment (no, I´m not leaving the planet, for now…), is terrifying. The worst thing is that I need to move on, to change my life (once again) and keep searching for that lost light that left me long ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress and Trip Hell</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/stress-and-trip-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2005 18:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/stress-and-trip-hell/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I have to admit it: traveling makes me nervous. Specially when going to an unknown place. Having a GPS has helped a little, but the main discovery is that people annoys me a lot. Consequences? A bad stomach, pain in the back, and most important, not being able to taste local food marvels… I need to find a solution for this fast!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football again…</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/football-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2005 17:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/football-again/</guid>
      <description>In this country, the best entertainment is to watch football matches (or, in the region where I live, going to the mountains… how boring). Today, the local team has the chance to win a trophy for the first time. They’re going to lose, of course, because the team that they will play against is better and stronger. But this is no handicap for the people to find a reason to get drunk, shout, party and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One of those days…</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/one-of-those-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2005 19:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/one-of-those-days/</guid>
      <description>This is one of that kind of horrible days when everything seems to be normal, but it´s not. Normally, this happens after a good one or two days of success and strong motivation, strange. It’s that difficult to stay focused and concentrated? I simply can´t. It’s like having a sixth sense warning you all the time, like if you can´t see the light at the end of the tunnel, never. The only relief is to know that some calm and relaxed days are on their way, aren´t they?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it really true?</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/is-it-really-true/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2005 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/is-it-really-true/</guid>
      <description>Is it true that you are “that” smart? Is it really possible to reach every and each one of your wishes and dreams? (by the way, Are they really yours?), are you obliged to get all the goals that your parents and friends and relatives are putting on you? What happens if you simply want to stop and think about your life? This remembers me of the beginning of the Trainspotting movie: What if you don’t want to live that way?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop fighting with yourself and live!</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/stop-fighting-with-yourself-and-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2005 20:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/stop-fighting-with-yourself-and-live/</guid>
      <description>Many times I have questioned myself about if I´m doing it right. I often compare my life with others that I consider “better”. How stupid. Doing this only produces two things: emptiness and frustration. I feel that I have let pass many special and unique moments only for trying to comply with everyone´s wishes. I think I should listen to myself with attention, to discover the things that I love and hate, to start learning how to live with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking calmly to nowhere</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/walking-calmly-to-nowhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2005 15:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/walking-calmly-to-nowhere/</guid>
      <description>Today is one of those horrible days in which I feel completely alone, useless and bored. That dark and dense feeling of emptiness, the incapacity of fitting in. So, I stumbled upon this. It´s weird and produces a strange sensation to find people that stores so many secrets, and see that they´re brave enough to share them, anonymously, though. It´s a kind of relief to see that I´m not the only one not willing to share those dark things that lurk in my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Paul II´s legacy</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/john-paul-iis-legacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2005 20:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/john-paul-iis-legacy/</guid>
      <description>I´ve been following (with more or less interest), all the things that have surrounded the Pope´s death. It was really curious to see many world politic and religious leaders meeting at St. Peter Square, shaking hands and sharing a little chat like they were old friends. As usual, this is only diplomatic stuff, nobody really cares about their neighbours, and everything will remain the same after a couple of days: war, religious differences and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill them all! (no, wait!)</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/kill-them-all-no-wait/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2005 14:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/kill-them-all-no-wait/</guid>
      <description>Human beings don´t stop to amaze me (but not in the best way, I must admit), specially when I realize that many of us simply don´t show any trace of respect or “fair behavior” with each other… I deeply hate the people that, for example, park their cars using two or more (!) parking places. Parking is getting more and more difficult here in Europe these days, (I´m starting to believe that buying a car is the people´s ultimate goal in their lives, or something), and those morons only think in themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fortunate Lives</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fortunate-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2005 03:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fortunate-lives/</guid>
      <description>Look at you for a moment. What do you see? I think I know the answer: you probably punish yourself too hard. “I see worries, that I’m ugly/fat/tall/short, problems, not enough money”;. Have you stopped only once to think that you are surrounded by people with lots of trouble, sickness, that do drugs, smoke, trapped in alcoholism, workoholic, with very dark and dramatic stories behind, and they do continue to run their lives in the way they can?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here we go…</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/here-we-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2005 16:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/here-we-go/</guid>
      <description>Yes, thanks to a dear friend, I finally made it to the net. It´s been a hard way, since my knowledge in these matters is really limited, but I wanted to open my mind to the world, to say many things that I think that should be out there, and not only for myself. Let´s see what happens. Please enjoy…</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>