<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts on Inner Daemons</title>
    <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/tags/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughts on Inner Daemons</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 | For those Daemons inside us</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 23:44:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.innerdaemons.com/tags/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fearful Blues</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fearful-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 23:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fearful-blues/</guid>
      <description>It happens from time to time. Everything seems to be going smoothly and then, a dark and long shadow appears out of nowhere (well, it comes from the same place almost all the times), to haunt me yet again. I used to think that as long as I did well and the years just passed, accumulating experience, the shadow was less likely to return. I was wrong again. Perhaps the only thing left to do is to just accept its existence and deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellusive Happiness</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/ellusive-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 04:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/ellusive-happiness/</guid>
      <description>Life is strange. The most important things happen in the wrong moments, it seems. One chapter ends, another begins but it feels like nothing it’s in place. There’s something always missing. Something not finished or not completely done. Why wait? I keep telling myself? Why not? Something inside me says “Let go, totally and freely. Don’t be afraid”, nonetheless when I feel so happy and comfortable with a supposedly “wrong situation” the question lingers again: “What should I do then?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fleeting moments</title>
      <link>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fleeting-moments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 02:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.innerdaemons.com/fleeting-moments/</guid>
      <description>It’s kind of weird to feel I’m in the eye of the storm. She sleeps peacefully with our cat on her side and I feel free and content just for a brief period of time, feeling that all our problems, fights, disagreements, tears, sadness and crazy feelings just don’t exist. It’s like observing them from a far distance, watching them in a blurry fashion. Perhaps life is about these moments and nothing else.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>